Fred Snitzer collection of Kings County Postal ephemera 2013.003
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Memorabilia, 1717-2002; 1880-1900; 1.5 Linear Feet in 2 oversized manucsript boxes and 1 record carton
  - Van Brunt - New Utrecht deed (2 folders), 1717-2002 (Box 38, Folder 8-9)
  - Index to bills and receipts (2 boxes), circa 1990s (Box 41)
- Series 4: Reference, 1860-2008; 1890-2008; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 oversized manuscript boxes and 1 record carton
  The series contains reference material related to philately and postal history (United States, New York state, and Kings County). It includes books, newsletters (Long Island Postal History Society, 1990s), collecting guides, auction catalogs, and clippings.
  - Reference files, 1860-2008 (Box 41, Box 40, Box 39)